beautybrite.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy | Beauty Brite

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to beautybrite.com and Beauty Brite and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Beauty Brite include beautybrite.com. The Beauty Brite website is a Lifestyle Blog site. By using the Beauty Brite website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

 _Collection of your Personal Information_

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Beauty Brite may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

– First and Last Name  
– Mailing Address  
– E-mail Address  
– Phone Number

Beauty Brite may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:

– Age  
– Gender

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Beauty Brite’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

 _Use of your Personal Information_

Beauty Brite collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Beauty Brite may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Beauty Brite and its affiliates.

Sharing Information with Third Parties

Beauty Brite does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Beauty Brite may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Beauty Brite may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Beauty Brite, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Beauty Brite may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Beauty Brite or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Beauty Brite; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Beauty Brite, or the public.

 _Automatically Collected Information_

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Beauty Brite. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Beauty Brite website.

 _Use of Cookies_

The Beauty Brite website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Beauty Brite pages, or register with Beauty Brite site or services, a cookie helps Beauty Brite to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Beauty Brite website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Beauty Brite features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Beauty Brite services or websites you visit. Visit our [Cookie policy](https://beautybrite.com/cookie-policy/).

 _Links_

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

 _Security of your Personal Information_

Beauty Brite secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Beauty Brite uses the following methods for this purpose:

– SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

 _Children Under Thirteen_

Beauty Brite does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

 _E-mail Communications_

From time to time, Beauty Brite may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Beauty Brite or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Beauty Brite, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button..

 _Changes to this Statement_

Beauty Brite reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

 _Contact Information_

Beauty Brite welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Beauty Brite has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Beauty Brite at:

Beauty Brite

Effective as of May 25, 2018
